(お通)みんな
こんばんわきが治療！
そして今日 最後の勝負で➡
二本目の魅力対決は 私を➡
寺門通親衛隊の勝ち！
すてきなｶﾝﾀﾞｰﾗ･ﾌﾞﾎﾃﾙに
誘ってくれた➡
すみません
おしっこ行ってきていいですか？
寺門通のｵﾌｨｼｬﾙﾌｧﾝｸﾗﾌﾞ
決定戦場のﾋﾟｱﾆｽﾄも➡
一本目のｸｲｽﾞ対決は
通選組の近藤さんが➡
ﾔﾀﾞ なんだか私のほうが
緊張してきちゃった！
私への真の愛を示してくれるのは
いったい どっち？
ﾊﾟｰﾌｪｸﾄにきつかったので
やっぱり 通選組の勝利！
やっぱり なかなか まだまだ 全然
ﾘｱﾙでは ＣＤが出ない私｡
残すところ本戦三本勝負｡
ﾗｽﾄ１戦のみのもんた！
Hey, everybody! Good nightingale!
I'm still having so much trouble releasing a CD in real life.
And there's only one match left in the three-match pianist battle
to decide Tsu Terakado's official fan club!
In the first match, the quiz showdown,
Kondo-san made a perfect read to deliver victory for the Tsusengumi!
In the second match, the charisma showdown,
victory went to the Tsu Terakado Fan Club who invited me to the Gandara Vehotel!
And today will be the last match!
Which team will show their true love for me?
Aww!
Now I'm starting to get nervous!
Sorry, can I go take a piss?
♪♪～
[ﾏｲｸ]寺門通ｵﾌｨｼｬﾙﾌｧﾝｸﾗﾌﾞ決定戦
本戦三本勝負｡
The three-match contest to decide Tsu Terakado's official fan club
いよいよ
最後の対決を迎えました！
has finally reached its final match!
多数のﾌｧﾝたちとの競争のなか➡
Only two teams out of the many fans made it to the finals!
本戦へとｺﾏを進めたのは
たった２ﾁｰﾑ｡
寺門通親衛隊！
The Tsu Terakado Fan Club!
かたや
前評判どおりの強さを見せつけ➡
On the other side, we have the team led by Mr. Toshi, which has lived up to its name!
勝ち抜いてきた ﾄｯｼｰ氏率いる➡
通選組！
The Tsusengumi!
ここまでは １勝１敗｡
Each team has one win and one loss.
互いに一進一退の攻防を
繰り広げてきましたが➡
We've been watching a back-and-forth battle here,
すべては
この一戦にて決まります｡
but everything will be decided by this final match!
今 最後の戦いが
始まろうとしています！
Now, the final battle will begin!
両ﾁｰﾑ代表者 ﾘﾝｸﾞ上へ！
Representatives from both teams enter the ring!
["Love Is Unconditional"]
(銀時)新八｡
Shinpachi.
ｵﾚたちにできることは
もう何もねえ｡
There's nothing left for us to do.
こっからは ﾃﾒｴの戦いだ｡
From here on, this is your battle.
I can't lose.
《新八:負けられない｡
負けるわけにはいかない｡
I can't afford to lose.
ﾎﾞｸを ここまで引きあげてくれた
みんなのためにも➡
For the sake of everyone who's helped bring me here,
ﾎﾞｸは 絶対に勝つ！》
I absolutely have to win!
(土方)世話んなったな
今度 なんかおごるわ｡
You've been a big help.
I'll buy you dinner some time.
(近藤)ﾄｼ 負けたら承知せんぞ｡
Toshi, failure is not allowed.
取り戻してこい 自分という存在を
その手に取り戻してこい！
Take back your own self with your own hands!
《ｵﾚは ｵﾀｸの頂点に立つ｡
I will stand above all otaku.
必ず ﾄｯｼｰから
この体を 取り戻してみせる》
I will take this body back from Toshi.
♪♪～
(２人)決着をつけよう！
Let's finish this.
三本目 最終対決で試されるのは
ｺﾚｸｼｮﾝ力｡
The third and final match will test your collecting abilities!
え？ ﾎﾞｸｼﾝｸﾞじゃないの？
We aren't boxing?
愛する お通ちゃんのｸﾞｯｽﾞなら
なんでも取り揃えているのは➡
As fans, you naturally have assembled all kinds of paraphernalia
ﾌｧﾝとして 当然のこと｡
related to your dear Otsu-chan.
どれだけ ﾏﾆｱｯｸなところまで
お通ちゃんｸﾞｯｽﾞを集めているか｡
How hardcore have you been in gathering Otsu-chan paraphernalia?
それが 今回のｷｰになります｡
That will be the key to this contest!
今回 扱うのは これ お通ﾁｯﾌﾟｽ！
This is what we will be using today, Otsu chips!
[ﾏｲｸ]お通ﾁｯﾌﾟｽ
売れ行きが微妙というか➡
Otsu chips!
Chips that aren't selling very well, or quite frankly, they aren't selling at all.
全然売れてない このﾁｯﾌﾟｽ｡
We will have a card battle using the bonus cards that come with these chips!
このお通ﾁｯﾌﾟｽについている
おまけｶｰﾄﾞで➡
ｶｰﾄﾞﾊﾞﾄﾙをしてもらいます！
ｶ ｶｰﾄﾞﾊﾞﾄﾙだって!?
(ざわめき)
A-A card battle?!
[ﾏｲｸ]ﾙｰﾙは簡単！
The rules are simple.
さまざまな お通ちゃんの姿が
接写された このｶｰﾄﾞ｡
These cards have images of Otsu-chan in various poses.
The cards have been assigned AP, attack points, and DP, defense points.
このｶｰﾄﾞには
それぞれ ＡＰ ｱﾀｯｸﾎﾟｲﾝﾄ｡
ＤＰ ﾃﾞｨﾌｪﾝｽﾎﾟｲﾝﾄというものが
設けられております｡
なんでｱｲﾄﾞﾙｶｰﾄﾞに
攻撃力と防御力があるわけ!?
Why would idol cards have attack power and defense power?!
[ﾏｲｸ]これを このﾗｲﾌﾞｽﾃｰｼﾞにｾｯﾄし…！
We will place them on this live stage...
♪♪～
[ﾏｲｸ]立体化させたお通ちゃんを
互いに戦わせます！
And you will fight through these holograms of Otsu-chan!
だから なんで戦わせるんだよ!?
しかも お通ちゃん同士!?
Why is fighting even involved?!
And between two Otsu-chans?!
[ﾏｲｸ]両者に与えれたＬＰは 2000Ｐ｡
Each player will be given 2000 life points.
For each turn, you will each use a card,
毎ﾀｰﾝごとに互いにｶｰﾄﾞを出し➡
そのﾊﾞﾄﾙに応じて
ＬＰが消費されていきます｡
and the corresponding number of life points will be spent.
先に ＬＰがｾﾞﾛになってしまった
ﾁｰﾑが敗北です！
The team whose life points reach zero first loses!
ちなみにｶｰﾄﾞは
こちらから支給しません！
And we won't be providing any cards!
ﾌｧﾝであれば このｶｰﾄﾞも
所有していて当たり前のはず！
As fans, you naturally have these cards on your person.
あなたたちが
現在所有するｶｰﾄﾞがそのまま➡
The cards you have on you right now will be your playing hand!
この勝負の
あなたたちの手札になります！
《ま まずい！
こんなｶｰﾄﾞ１枚も持ってないぞ！
N-Not good!
I don't have a single one of those cards!
持ってないどころか➡
Hell, I never even knew they were being sold!
発売していることすら
知らなかった！
And didn't that bag say it was Indian Corn-poop flavored?!
つうかさっき とうきびうんこ味
って書いてなかった!?
Are those even edible?!
食えんの それ!?
いや 待て…！
No, wait.
Hijikata-san couldn't possibly have any of these cards...
こんなｶｰﾄﾞ 土方さんだって
持っているわけがない！》
Please set your cards and shuffle!
[ﾏｲｸ]ｶｰﾄﾞをｾｯﾄし
ｼｬｯﾌﾙしてください！
ﾌﾝｯ！
ひ 土方～!!
Hi-Hijikata!
《なぜ お前がそれを！
Why do you have those?!
And so many!
しかも あんなにたくさん！
あの土方さんが…｡
あのｸｰﾙが売りの土方さんが➡
Hijikata-san, whose coolness is his strength,
お通ﾁｯﾌﾟｽｶｰﾄﾞを あんなにも～!!》
has that many Otsu chips cards!
《恥も外聞も捨て
それでもｵﾚは自分を取り戻す！
I will abandon shame and self-respect to take myself back.
生半可な覚悟で ｵﾀｸの覇王なんぞ
目指しはしないさ！》
You can't conquer the otaku world by being half-hearted.
《ｸｯ！ 土方さん 恐ろしき執念｡
Hijikata-san...
What dreadful tenacity...
This is bad...
まずい… ｶｰﾄﾞがないんじゃ
勝負にならない！》
I can't put up a fight without any cards!
♪♪～
それでは ﾃﾞｭｴﾙ開始！
(ｺﾞﾝｸﾞ)
Then, let the duel begin!
銀さん！ 売店へ！
Gin-san, run to the store!
Buy lots of Otsu chips right away!
お通ﾁｯﾌﾟｽを 今すぐ大量に
買ってきてください！
待っとけ！
ﾌﾝｯ｡
I'm on it!
So you didn't have any...as I expected.
やはり
持ち合わせていなかったか｡
今更 急づくろいで
ｶｰﾄﾞを揃えたところで 遅い！
It's too late to try and assemble a deck now!
ｵﾚは お通ﾁｯﾌﾟｽ第３ｼﾘｰｽﾞまでの
ｶｰﾄﾞをｺﾝﾌﾟﾘｰﾄしているんだ！
I have a complete set up to the third series of Otsu chips!
ｶｰﾄﾞが揃う前に
一気にかたをつけてやる！
I'll finish this before you get any cards!
ｵﾚのｶｰﾄﾞは これだ！
あっ!?
This is my card!
まずは通選組
ﾄｯｼｰ氏がしかけた！
Mr. Toshi from the Tsusengumi makes the first move!
His card is!
[ﾏｲｸ]ｶｰﾄﾞは!?
Sentimental five minutes before curtain.
Otsu in her dressing room right before the beginning of a concert.
She's a nervous wreck.
She will indiscriminately attack anyone if given the opportunity.
(Especially Kimura.)
460 attack points.
3 defense points.
What kind of card is that?!
どんなｶｰﾄﾞだ!!
You're revealing way too much stuff people don't want to hear about an idol!
ｱｲﾄﾞﾙのｲﾔなとこ
赤裸々に書きすぎだろ!?
つうか 木村って誰!?
And who the hell is Kimura?!
[ﾏｲｸ]これは ﾄｯｼｰ氏 しょっぱなから
攻撃的なｶｰﾄﾞを繰り出してきた！
Mr. Toshi has chosen an attack card to begin with!
♪♪～
(お通)ｳﾌｯ…｡
楽屋に勝手に
入ってくんじゃねえ!!
Don't come in my dressing room without permission!
うっ… なんで立体映像が
生身の人間に➡
Why is a hologram attacking a real person?!
直接攻撃してきてんの!?
おっと！ つうか これ誰だ!?
再現率 低すぎだろ!!
And who the hell is she?!
This doesn't look anything like the original!
まったく別人じゃねえか！ うっ！
She looks like a totally different person!
志村氏 立体化したお通ちゃんに
なすすべがありません！
Mr. Shimura can do nothing against the Otsu-chan hologram!
志村氏のﾀｰﾝです｡
早急に手を打たなければ➡
It is Mr. Shimura's turn!
If he doesn't make a move, he'll lose a large number of life points
大幅にﾗｲﾌﾎﾟｲﾝﾄを
減らすことになります！
新八！
あっ！
Shinpachi!
銀さん 間に合った！
ｶｰﾄﾞを選別してる暇はない！
Gin-san!
You made it in time!
I don't have time to choose a card!
これで いけ！
I'll go with this!
あっ！
うわっ！
Oh!
あっと これは… このｶｰﾄﾞは！
This is...!
This card is...!
♪♪～
ｶｰﾄﾞを選別してる暇はない！
I don't have time to choose a card!
これで いけ！
I'll go with this!
あっ！
うわっ！
Oh!
あっと これは… このｶｰﾄﾞは！
This is...!
This card is...!
あっと～ このｶｰﾄﾞは！
Oh! This card is...!
ぐっ… えっ!?
KIM!
[ﾏｲｸ]KIMです！ ﾍﾞｰｽのKIMです！
KIM the bass player!
いや 誰!?
Uh, who the hell is that?!
KIM the bass player.
A member of Otsu's backing band, which supports Otsu behind the scenes.
The bass player who also occasionally plays the castanets.
Why does it feel like I pulled a pointlessly plain card?!
なんか すげぇ どうでもいい
地味なｶｰﾄﾞ引いちゃったよ！
What are its attack points?!
ｱﾀｯｸﾎﾟｲﾝﾄは!?
なんか特殊能力とかないの？
Does it have some kind of special ability?!
The mole on his face occasionally vanishes,
but he's an enigmatic figure who remains silent when asked about it.
(And his real name isn't KIM, but Chutaro Kimura.)
木村じゃねえか!!
So it's Kimura!
It's the Kimura that Otsu-chan is always spazzing on about!
これ さっき お通ちゃんに
八つ当たりされてた木村だろ!?
He was clearly getting his mole taken off by Otsu-chan!
明らかに お通ちゃんに
ﾎｸﾛとられかけてんだろ！
このｶｰﾄﾞは ｱﾀｯｸﾎﾟｲﾝﾄ！
ﾃﾞｨﾌｪﾝｽﾎﾟｲﾝﾄを持たない補助ｶｰﾄﾞ！
This card is a support card with no attack points or defense points!
その場にある
お通ｶｰﾄﾞすべてをｲﾗつかせ➡
Its effect is to piss off all Otsu cards in play and double their attack points!
ｱﾀｯｸﾎﾟｲﾝﾄを倍にする効果を持つ！
Sentimental five minutes before curtain's attack points have doubled to 920!
｢開幕５分前の憂鬱｣
ｱﾀｯｸﾎﾟｲﾝﾄ 920に倍加｡
おい！ 何なんだよ そのﾎｸﾛ！
Hey, what's with the mole?
なんかのｽｲｯﾁか？ あぁ!?
えっ？
Is it some kind of switch?
It's a damn eyesore!
目障りなんだよ！ うらぁ！
おぉ～！ ぐはっ！
志村氏 痛恨のﾐｽ！
Mr. Shimura makes a painful mistake!
あろうことか補助ｶｰﾄﾞで
相手のｶｰﾄﾞの攻撃力を倍加｡
He ended up using a support card to double the attack power of his opponent's card!
ﾗｲﾌﾎﾟｲﾝﾄを
半分近く削られてしまいました！
He has lost nearly half of his life points!
Shinpachi!
[Note: Kagura and Gintoki are dressed as Danpei, who is the manager and corner man from boxing manga Tomorrow's Joe (Ashita no Joe).]
(神楽)新八！
何してんだ ﾊﾞｶﾀﾚ！
What are you doing, fool?!
You gotta throw inside punches!
もっと内角に えぐりこむように！
[ﾏｲｸ]しかも 補助ｶｰﾄﾞ ﾍﾞｰｽのKIMは
５ﾀｰﾝもの間 効果が持続します！
And this support card, KIM the bass player, lasts for five turns!
おい 帰れ！ 木村 ﾃﾒｴ！
Hey, scram!
Stupid Kimura!
[ﾏｲｸ]次ﾀｰﾝも倍加した
ｱﾀｯｸﾎﾟｲﾝﾄで攻撃されれば➡
If Mr. Shimura is attacked by a card with doubled attack points in the next turn,
もはや 志村氏に
勝機はありません！
he has no chance of victory!
くっ…｡
(土方)ﾌｯ…
倍加で済めばいいがな｡
As if double attack power was all you had to worry about.
あっ！
ｵﾚのﾀｰﾝ！
My turn!
補助ｶｰﾄﾞの本当の使い方ってやつを
ﾃﾒｴに教えてやるぜ！
I'll teach you how you're supposed to use support cards!
This is my next card!
次のｶｰﾄﾞは これだ！
あっと～
このｶｰﾄﾞは ｢あの日｣だ～！
Oh!
This card is...!
That day of the month!
That day of the month.
Aggravate all female cards and triple their attack points.
However, you cannot play a card the next time.
Which day is that day of the month?!
あの日って どの日だ！
これﾎﾝﾄに ｱｲﾄﾞﾙのｶｰﾄﾞｹﾞｰﾑか？
Is this really an idol card game?!
つうか 放送していいのか これ！
And is it actually okay to show this on TV?!
ﾄｯｼｰ氏 ﾍﾞｰｽのKIMで
ｲﾗ立つお通ちゃんを更に➡
Mr. Toshi has added that day of the month to an Otsu-chan
あの日に
重ねることで最悪の機嫌に！
already irritated by KIM the bass player to leave her in the worst possible mood!!
♪♪～
What?!
なんと その攻撃力たるや 2760！
And her attack power is now 2,760!
An amazing number!
すさまじい数値です！ 志村氏
この攻撃をまともに受ければ➡
If Mr. Shimura is hit with an attack, he'll lose in one blow!
一撃で敗北必至です｡
なんとかしなくちゃ！
I have to do something!
新八！ お通ﾁｯﾌﾟｽ追加だ！
Shinpachi!
Here's more Otsu chips!
出ろ！ いいｶｰﾄﾞ出てくれ！
Come on!
Give me a good card!
銀さん これﾎﾝﾄに
お通ﾁｯﾌﾟｽなんですか？
Gin-san.
Are these really Otsu chips?
木村ﾁｯﾌﾟｽの
間違いなんじゃないですか？
Are you sure you didn't get Kimura chips by accident?
新八！ 手札は５枚までだ！
最後の１枚にかけろ！
Shinpachi!
You can only have five cards in a hand!
Bet everything on the last one!
An Otsu card!
《お通ｶｰﾄﾞだ｡ ﾎﾞｸも
お通ｶｰﾄﾞを引き当てるんだ！
I'm going to draw an Otsu card!
お通ｶｰﾄﾞがあれば ﾍﾞｰｽの｢KIM｣
｢あの日｣の効果をﾎﾞｸも受けて➡
If I have an Otsu card,
I can receive the effects from KIM the bass player and that day of the month
and put up a fight against that monster!
あの化け物に対抗できる！》
ﾑﾀﾞだ！ ちょっとや
そっとの小細工じゃ➡
It's no use.
Cheap tricks won't do anything against this strike.
この一撃どうにもならん！
いけ！ あの日のお通！
Go!
Otsu on that day of the month!
ｸﾘｰﾝﾋｯﾄ！ 志村氏
ｱﾀｯｸﾎﾟｲﾝﾄ 2760の攻撃を➡
A clean hit!
Mr. Shimura has taken a direct 2,760 attack hit!
まともにくらってしまった！
(ざわめき)
ﾌｯ 勝負あったな｡
It's all over.
Wh-What?!
な なにっ？
I-Impossible!
ﾊﾞ ﾊﾞｶな お前…｡
You...
Why are you...
なぜ お前がそこにいる！
Over there?!
おっと なんと補助ｶｰﾄﾞ
ﾍﾞｰｽのKIMが 志村氏の身代わりに！
Oh!
The support card, KIM the bass player, took the hit for Mr. Shimura!
Impossible...
ﾊﾞｶな…
補助ｶｰﾄﾞであるはずのお前が➡
How could a support card like you enter combat...?
ﾊﾞﾄﾙに参加することなど まして➡
Much less endure a 2,760 attack point hit...!
ｱﾀｯｸﾎﾟｲﾝﾄ 2760の攻撃を
耐えしのぐなど…｡
あっ！ あ あれは…｡
That's...
まさか！
It can't be!
Separation..
A support card that only works on KIM the bass player.
Sacrifice the mole to withstand one attack by Otsu-chan.
ｷ KIMさん！
K-KIM-san!
なんとﾍﾞｰｽのKIM
己のﾎｸﾛを犠牲にして➡
KIM the bass player sacrificed his mole to protect Mr. Shimura!
志村氏を守り通した！
ま まさか  そんな手があるとは｡
I-It can't be!
I didn't expect that!
ﾄｯｼｰ氏 あの日のｶｰﾄﾞで
次ﾀｰﾝはｶｰﾄﾞが出せません｡
Mr. Toshi cannot use a card next turn because of that day of the month!
これは一気に形勢逆転したか？
Have the tables been turned?!
KIM-san, hang in there!
KIMさん しっかりしてください！
ﾎｸﾛのかたきを と…｡
Avenge my mole...
KIMさん！ ﾎｸﾛ取れただけですよ！
KIM-san!
You just lost your mole!
しっかりしてください！
何で？ 意味わかんない！
Hang in there!
Why?!
I don't get it!
さあ 再び志村氏のﾀｰﾝ｡
このﾁｬﾝｽは 絶対に逃せない！
Okay, it's Mr. Shimura's turn again!
He can't let this chance slip away!
是が非でも
いいｶｰﾄﾞを引かなければ！
He must draw a good card by any means!
《土方さんは補助ｶｰﾄﾞも使えない
完全無防備状態｡
Hijikata-san is completely helpless, unable to use a support card.
畳み掛けるのは今しかない｡
This is my chance to strike back!
お通ちゃんｶｰﾄﾞだ
今度こそ お通ちゃんｶｰﾄﾞを｡
An Otsu-chan card!
Draw an Otsu-chan card this time!
Please!
頼む 来い！
Come on!
来い！
Oh! This is...
あ これは！ あのｶｰﾄﾞは！
That card is...!
KIYOSHI ﾄﾞﾗﾑのKIYOSHIだ｡
KIYOSHI!
KIYOSHI the drummer!
また どうでもよさそうなの
出てきた！
I got another worthless-looking one!
KIYOSHI the drummer.
A member of Otsu's backing band, which supports Otsu behind the scenes.
The drummer who also occasionally plays the tambourine.
He used to be close with KIM the bass player,
but they got in a fight the other day when someone ate an extra slice of pizza,
and they're looking for an opportunity to make up.
Who cares about that?!
どうでもいいわ！ 楽屋でやれ
ｹﾞｰﾑに持ち込んでくるな！
Do that stuff in the dressing room!
Don't bring it into the game!
ﾋﾟｻﾞｶｰﾄﾞがあれば
KIMと仲直りしｾｯｼｮﾝができる｡
If you have a pizza card, they'll make up and have a session.
どうでもいいって言ってんだろ！
Like I said, who cares?!
Or if you have a cash card, they'll become even closer than they were before.
もしくは 現金ｶｰﾄﾞがあれば
前よりも仲よくなれる｡
金で解決すんな！
Don't use money to settle it!
あっ！
(KIM)なんだよ
こっち見てんじゃねえよ｡
What is it?
Don't look this way.
(KIYOSHI)
え？ べつに見てないけど｡
I wasn't looking at you.
超気まずいんですけど
何なの？ ｺｲﾂら｡
This is really awkward.
What's with these guys?
何しに出てきたんだよ｡
Why did they show up?
ﾌﾌﾌﾌ どうやらせっかくのﾁｬﾝｽ➡
It appears that he wasn't able to take advantage of his lucky chance.
まったく活かすことが
できなかったようだな｡
もうお前に
勝機が訪れることはない｡
You have no chance of victory now.
とうとう
このときがやってきたようだな｡
The time has finally come.
長かったぜ 妖刀を手にし➡
It's been a long time.
その呪いにとり憑かれて以来
ようやく…｡
After obtaining that demonic sword and becoming cursed,
どんなに必死に押さえ込んでも
隙を見ては現れる ｵﾚの分身 ﾄｯｼｰ｡
I had to frantically suppress my other self, Toshi, who would pop up at any chance...
気づかぬ間に増えていく
ﾌｨｷﾞｭｱやＤＶＤの山｡
The next thing I knew, I had a growing pile of figures and DVDs...
見知らぬｵﾀｸに
町で声をかけられるという日々｡
And was being greeted on the street by strange otaku on a daily basis...
I will end it all with this blow!
この一撃で
すべては終わりを告げる｡
このｶｰﾄﾞで ｵﾚは
すべてを終わらせてやる！
I'll end it all with this card!
これで しめえだ！
This is...the end!
いっけえ！
Go!
MIYABI the stylist.
A stylist with a bad attitude.
Regularly eats and steals stuff from the dressing room without permission.
Otsu's deadly foe.
Only works on Otsu in dressing room cards.
Plus 1,000 attack points and defense points.
(MIYABI)ﾑﾌ ﾌﾌ ﾑﾎﾎﾎﾎﾎ！
うおぉ～!!
(土方)今度こそおしまいだ
覚悟はいいか｡
This time, it's over.
You ready?
《さすがは戦術の鬼 土方十四郎｡
As expected from the brilliant strategist, Toshiro Hijikata...
あれよあれよと
ここまで追い込まれてしまった｡
He has me completely backed into a corner.
だけど ﾎﾞｸだって
負けるわけにはいかないんだ｡
But...
I can't afford to lose!
ﾎﾞｸを助けてくれた
みんなの気持｡
The feelings of everyone who has helped me...
銀さん 神楽ちゃん｡
Gin-san, Kagura-chan...
そして ﾀｶﾃｨﾝ
…に たかちん｡
And Taka-tin.
Plus Taka-chin.
そして 何より お通ちゃんを
宇宙一 愛していると信じている➡
And most importantly...
My feelings of love and complete trust in Otsu-chan...
ﾎﾞｸの気持を…》
裏切るわけにはいかないんだ！
I can't let them down!
このｶｰﾄﾞに ﾎﾞｸのすべてを懸ける｡
I'll stake my all on this card!
A mystery investigating card?!
Reveal a hidden truth to change parameters!
Damn it.
ｸｿ！ 最後まで微妙なｶｰﾄﾞが｡
Another weird card in the end...
ｸｯｸｯｸｯｸｯ… 万策尽きたな｡
You're out of options.
死ね!!
Die!
ｸｿｯ！ こうなりゃ
神頼みだ!! いけ！
Damn it!
I'll just have to leave it to fate!
Go!
(天の声)謎追求ｶｰﾄﾞ 発動｡
Mystery investigating card activate.
Allow me to tell you the hidden truth.
隠された真実をお教えしましょう｡
あなたたちのﾋﾟｻﾞを
つまみ食いしたのは…｡
The one who secretly ate your pizza...
あなたたちのﾋﾟｯﾂｧを
つまみ食いしたのは…｡
The one who secretly ate your pizza...
このﾃﾞﾌﾞです｡
Was this fatass!
ﾜﾝ ﾄｩｰ ﾜﾝ ﾄｩｰ ３ ４！
Ichi, ni...
Ichi, ni, three, four!
♪♪～
Begin makeup session.
うお～っ!!
♪♪～
これは…｡
This is...
[ﾏｲｸ]｢仲直りｾｯｼｮﾝ｣
世界平和の願いが込められた演奏｡
Makeup session.
A performance to bring peace on Earth!
こちらからは攻撃できないが
攻撃を仕掛けられた場合…｡
You are unable to attack, but if you're attacked,
♪♪～
[ﾏｲｸ]ｱﾀｯｸﾎﾟｲﾝﾄを倍加し
その攻撃を跳ね返す！
the attack points are doubled and the attack is reflected!
(２人)うお～っ!!
[To Be Continued]
[Shiruko and Zenzai]
You just sometimes get in the mood
for some hot shiruko, even when it isn't winter.
And yeah, I can't really tell the difference between shiruko and zenzai.
[Note: Zenzai(sweet bean soup): made from condensed paste with heat and is less watery than shiruko(red bean soup) which is more akin to jam or marmalade.]
Why do they have to make it so complicated?
Just call them the same name.
Why bother differentiating?
Yeah, it's hard to tell the difference.
And there's Yu Aoi and Sora Aoi.
[Note: Yu Aoi is a popular mainstream actress. Sora Aoi is a Japanese porn star.]
They might as well be the same person.
I get them confused at times.
No, their names just sound similar.
They're different people.
I'm thinking that they're talking about, y'know,
but then they're actually talking about some fancy movie.
It leaves my face burning.
I don't want to endure another ordeal like that.
And yeah, can Rinka clone herself or something?
[Note: Rinka is a Japanese model and TV personality.]
There are like five or six of them on TV.
I can't tell which one's which.
♪♪～
Can't they just combine into one giant Rinka?
And I can't tell the difference between GinTama and Kintama.
[Note: Kintama is slang for "balls" in Japanese.]
冬場じゃなくても
たまに無性に食いたくなるよな｡
Which one's the right ball and which one's the left ball?
汁粉って｡
[The End]
つうか 汁粉と善哉の違いが
よく わかんねえんだけど ｵﾚ｡
[Preview]
Thanks, Toshiro...
紛らわしいよ｡
もう いいだろ？ 一緒で｡
But that's enough...
なんで かたくなに
呼び方 分けてるわけ？
I'll handle the rest...
いや 確かに
よくわかんないですよね｡
The next episode...
あと 蒼井優と蒼井そらも｡
"The Black Ships Even Make A Scene When They Sink."
[Toshi dangerously appears from within Toshiro! On to the next showdown in the Official Fan Club battle!]
ｱｲﾂら 一緒でいいだろ？
たまに ｺﾞﾁｬｺﾞﾁｬになんだよ｡
いや 名前 似てるだけで
別人ですよね？
[By the way, there are many differences between Shiruko and Zenzai depending on whether you're in the Kanto or Kansai area. Google them for more details.]
あっちの話だと思って
のっかったら➡
向こう ｵｼｬﾚ映画の話
してたりとかさ｡ もう赤っ恥だよ｡
[See you next time.]
あんな悲劇は
もう繰り返しちゃいけないよ｡
あとさ 梨花って
分身の術とか使えるの？
ﾃﾚﾋﾞに ５ ６人 梨花 出てるよね？
もう どれがどれだが
全然わかんねえよ｡
早く合体して １体の巨大梨花に
なってくれねえかな｡
あと 銀魂と金玉も
よくわからないｱﾙ｡
どっちが右の玉で
どっちが左の玉ｱﾙか？